#
MRN
Brief history
Responsible  Physician
Discussion Points
1.
A 53 y/o female patient with newly diagnosed to have LT Breast IDC- ER-positive, PR-negative , HER2-negative Ki 67-25%
Dr. Marwan
Approach?
2.
110995
A 28 y/o female patient with multiple RT Breast masses.Operated twice by local excisions, Then underwent Mastectomy. Pathology showed sarcoma
Dr. Marwan
Adjuvant therapy?
3.
111051
A 66 y/o male patient, Known case or recurrent GIST. S/p surgical resection. On 02.26 he had disease recurrence at the bed of surgery in the upper abdomen. On neoadjuvant Imatinib. Baseline Pet CT- pending result
Dr.Wasim
Best approach?
4.
112958
A 65 year old female patient, right side facial melanoma, cervical lymph nodes, thyroid nodules. 
https://view.stradus.com/?#PteQqPxuvn9ZsYe0YmxmpxC
https://view.stradus.com/?#Pp4ZeKKybfqIMcGrONww6jY
Dr.Hanna
Stage of disease?
Next step?
5.
A 25 y/o  male patient , newly diagnosed with GCT.   s/p left orchiectomy-pathology showed Embryonal carcinoma T2,LVI present, Tumor markers normal. Staging CT showed at least two left para aortic lymph nodes measuring up to 8mm. 
Dr. Salah
Image review and best treatment approach 
6.
104576
A57 y/o male patient with left lung adenocarcinoma T4N2, molecular profile negative, post definitive chemoradiation 8 months ago with great response. Now left adrinal lesion 2 cm with pathological uptake
Dr. Ibrahim
Adrinalectomy vs SBRT to left adrenal gland?
